Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪
[The Sparrow's Gambit]
[مناورة العصفور]
Twelve years ago,
منذ اثني عشر عامًا،
you killed my family,
لقد قتلت عائلتي
disfigured my face,
شوهت وجهي،
falsely claimed to be my savior,
ادعى زوراً أنه منقذي،
blinded my eyes,
أعميت عيني
and deceived me from the truth.
وخدعني عن الحقيقة.
For twelve years,
لمدة اثني عشر عاما،
you seized my family's wealth,
لقد استولت على ثروة عائلتي،
humiliated and abused me,
أذلني وأساء إلي،
and famed me for opium trafficking,
واشتهرت بتهريب الأفيون،
making me die unjustly.
جعلني أموت ظلماً.
Twelve years later,
بعد اثني عشر عامًا،
all sins will be repaid.
سيتم التكفير عن جميع الذنوب.
I
أنا
have returned.
لقد عادوا.
[Episode 1]
[الحلقة 1]
[One month ago]
[منذ شهر واحد]
[Blycher Hotel]
[فندق بليشر]
Move along now.
تحرك الآن.
Go play over there.
اذهب للعب هناك.
Mr. Sun,
السيد صن،
this batch of opium
هذه الدفعة من الأفيون
will surely transport you to bliss.
سوف ينقلك بالتأكيد إلى النعيم.
Miss Wang, your legs are so fair,
آنسة وانغ، ساقيك جميلتان جدًا،
though somewhat cold.
على الرغم من أنه بارد إلى حد ما.
[Mr. Sun]
[السيد صن]
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
[Wang Wan'er, daughter of Wang Penghui] Wenbin will return home soon.
[وانغ وان إير، ابنة وانغ بينغوي] سوف تعود وينبين إلى المنزل قريبًا.
We are already engaged.
نحن مخطوبون بالفعل.
You'd better behave.
من الأفضل أن تتصرف بشكل جيد.
Keep your distance from me.
ابقي مسافة بينك وبيني .
Have you arranged the shipment?
هل قمت بترتيب الشحنة؟
All arranged.
تم ترتيب كل شيء.
Time and place are set.
تم تحديد الزمان والمكان.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
Is the transaction data secured?
هل بيانات المعاملة مؤمنة؟
All locked in the safe.
كلها مغلقة في الخزنة.
Finally found proof of their opium deal.
وأخيرًا تم العثور على دليل على صفقة الأفيون الخاصة بهم.
The Marshal of Song City is after opium?
هل يسعى عمدة مدينة سونغ وراء الأفيون؟
Then I shall lure him in.
ثم سأغريه بالدخول.
Someone is here.
هناك شخص هنا.
Go take a look.
اذهب وانظر.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
[Chen Wenbin, Marshal]
[تشين وينبين، المارشال]
[Liu Rumeng]
[ليو رومينج]
Boss, it was stolen!
يا رئيس، لقد سُرقت!
- What?
- ماذا؟
Seal the hotel now!
اغلق الفندق الآن!
The place is full of guards.
المكان مليء بالحراس.
You cannot escape.
لا يمكنك الهروب.
Work with me.
اعمل معي.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You exposed me,
لقد كشفتني
then you save me?
ثم تنقذني؟
Why?
لماذا؟
For you.
لك.
Marshal Chen is back in Song City!
المارشال تشين عاد إلى مدينة سونغ!
Wenbin,
وينبين،
is this flower for me?
هل هذه الزهرة لي؟
Boss, this is the man.
يا رئيس، هذا هو الرجل.
Why did you return without telling me?
لماذا عدت دون أن تخبرني؟
Sorry, sir.
عذرا سيدي.
Something important was stolen.
لقد تمت سرقة شيء مهم.
To catch the thief,
للقبض على اللص،
please
لو سمحت
work with us.
العمل معنا.
Shut up! Do you know who he is?
اسكت! هل تعرف من هو؟
He is the son of Song City Military Governor.
وهو ابن الحاكم العسكري لمدينة سونغ.
Chen Wenbin, Marshal Chen!
تشين وينبين، المارشال تشين!
[Invitation]
[دعوة]
And he is my fiancé.
وهو خطيبي.
I was blind.
لقد كنت أعمى.
My apologies,
اعتذاري،
Marshal Chen,
المارشال تشين،
Miss Wang.
السيدة وانغ.
[Memory of Lin Qingyi, Lin Wenruo, and Lin Zongyao]
[ذكرى لين تشينغي، لين وينرو، ولين زونغياو]
Do you want to know
هل تريد أن تعرف
who killed the Lin family back then?
من قتل عائلة لين في ذلك الوقت؟
It was my father.
لقد كان والدي.
Your so-called savior.
منقذك المزعوم.
He planned it.
لقد خطط لذلك.
[Lin Wenruo, father of Lin Qingyi]
[لين وينرو، والد لين تشينغي]
Qingmao,
تشينغماو,
my father said
قال والدي
as the Wang family's executioner,
باعتباره جلاد عائلة وانغ،
your life is a threat.
حياتك تشكل تهديدا.
Today you must die.
اليوم يجب أن تموت.
After the Lin family fire,
بعد حريق عائلة لين،
my father saved you.
لقد أنقذك والدي.
He let you live ten more years as Qingmao.
لقد سمح لك بالعيش لمدة عشر سنوات أخرى باعتبارك تشينغماو.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
in these ten years,
في هذه السنوات العشر،
seeing your ugly face
رؤية وجهك القبيح
in front of me
أمامي
made me sick?
جعلني مريضا؟
[Hua]
[فاكهة]
Meng,
منغ،
they are here.
إنهم هنا.
I have waited so long.
لقد انتظرت لفترة طويلة.
I finally lured you in.
لقد أغريتك أخيرا.
[The Paramount] The place looks nice.
[باراماونت] المكان يبدو لطيفًا.
Yes, so many people!
نعم الكثير من الناس!
It's really bustling.
إنه صاخب حقا.
Yeah.
نعم.
Just looks good.
يبدو جيدا.
Let's go in and see.
دعونا ندخل ونرى.
Sure, let's go.
بالتأكيد، دعنا نذهب.
Come on.
تعال.
The Paramount is now open,
تم افتتاح فندق باراماونت الآن،
cordially inviting you, Marshal Chen.
أدعوك بكل سرور، المارشال تشين.
Liu Rumeng.
ليو رومينج.
The Paramount?
الباراماونت؟
I will kill you.
سأقتلك.
The Chen military family!
عائلة تشين العسكرية!
The Wang merchant family!
عائلة التجار وانغ!
You worked together to kill my family!
لقد عملتما معًا لقتل عائلتي!
I will grind you to dust.
سأطحنك إلى غبار.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
The Paramount owner,
مالك شركة باراماونت،
Liu Rumeng.
ليو رومينج.
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪Magnolia petals fly across the sky♪
♪بتلات الماغنوليا تطير عبر السماء♪
♪Spring and autumn come and go♪
♪الربيع والخريف يأتيان ويذهبان♪
♪People gather and part♪
♪يتجمع الناس ويفترقون♪
♪How brave can one be with no regrets?♪
♪كيف يمكن للإنسان أن يكون شجاعًا دون أن يشعر بالندم؟♪
♪I will paint love and hate in the sky♪
♪سأرسم الحب والكراهية في السماء♪
♪Engraving my love for you♪
♪نقش حبي لك♪
♪I roam through this chaotic world♪
♪أتجول في هذا العالم الفوضوي♪
♪Who will guard me for life?♪
♪من سيحرسني طيلة حياتي؟♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪